testpassed.com 2016-10-30

# TestPassed's Privacy Policy

Welcome to the Privacy Center of TestPassed, **_TestPassed respects your privacy_ **. By this notice, we make a commitment to you that we' will protect your privacy. 

_In the following parts, we will show you how your data is collected and used._

_**Where Can Privacy Notice be used?** _

This privacy notice informs how TestPassed deals with the personal identification information and other personal identification information shared by the business companies when visitors visit [www.testpassed.com](http://www.testpassed.com/) and its server. 

When you are registered to be a member of TestPassed, it means that we can use your information according to this privacy notice.

**User E-mail and Password**

You are required to fill in your e-mail addresss and password when you register at TestPassed. The only one thing that matters when you log in is your password. Your registered E-mail is your username when you log in at [http://www.testpassed.com](http://www.testpassed.com/) . Please use an e-mail address which is effective so we can keep in touch with you. 

  * You can change your password once you have logged in TestPassed Login Area. 
  * If you forget your password, you may lose your account and your personal identification information. 
  * You can contact us or use the links for password missing to get your password back. 
  * TestPassed holds no responsibility for the damage caused by a missing password which is due to individual mistakes or improper use of the login area. 

**Collect Information**

When you register at TestPassed, use TestPassed's products or services, we'll collect your personal identification information.

If you want to be a member of TestPassed, you are required to fill in the information, including name and registered e-mail address.

In addition, if you choose the Products Delivery Service, you are required to fill in your true name, address, phone number and postal code.

TestPassed offers better service to its members by obtaining members' statistical information from this registered information.

**Use of Information**

TestPassed collects client's information to offer better focused services. After becoming a member of TestPassed, we will offer you the following services by checking your registered information: 

  * Enjoy TestPassed Membership Price. 
  * Receive the information of Sales Promotions of TestPassed periodically. 
  * Request assistance from our " [**Live Support**](http://www.testpassed.com/page_about.html) " 

**Proclaim and Share the Information**

TestPassed will never give, sell, rent or share our user's personal information with the third party unless following circumstances as exceptions:

  * When we are allowed to share the information with the third party by our clients. 
  * Whenever, without sharing your personal information, the products and services you need/require will not be possible to offer. 
  * When, the third party, the surrogate of TestPassed and TestPassed offer services together. (After the service, the third party is forbidden to read all the data which is available before the service included.) 
  * When we are forced to offer your information by law and the government. 
  * We find out that you disobey the service terms of TestPassed or rules of other products and services. 

**Use of Cookies**

Under the circumstances that you don't refuse to receive cookies, they will be sent to your browser and kept in the hard disk of your computer. 

We use cookies to store the data caused by visiting our website. So when you visit our website or visit it again, we can identify you. 

We can offer you better service by analyzing the data. You have the right to choose to accept the cookies or refuse it. You can also refuse cookies by changing settings of the browser. 

**IP**

We trace the IP just for the consideration of safety and we can learn about the installations of our products. The software products of TestPassed can only be installed in two different machines. If the active IP of users changes frequently, we will contact the clients and take measures to prevent the TestPassed products from being abused.

**Credit Card**

TestPassed online payment solution requires clients to fill in the information of credit card and submit it to finish the purchasing procedure. TestPassed will never get anything about the client's integrity payment information. All our online payment is accomplished by the third safe payment gateway. We can tell whether the client has successfully paid by the feedback information of the payment gateway. TestPassed only gets part of the payment information to keep in touch with clients with reason. TestPassed uses SSL confidential system to ensure the security of data transmission.

If our payment gateway judges that there might be some possibility of Credit Card Fraud, The client will receive a mail inquiring about the information of your credit card. You should respond it in 24 hours if you have received such mails. Then we will submit the information you offered to the payment gateway to prove that you're the cardholder of the credit card to dispel your suspicion of cheating. 

The information you offered will be reserved by us for three months in order to accomplish the payment with the bank. In the meantime, TestPassed ensures that your information won't be shared or exchanged. We will destroy all the information after three months to protect your privacy.

**External Links**

You may find some links to other websites in http://www.testpassed.com and TestPassed has no responsibility for other websites privacy safeguards. We may add some related business company's websites to TestPassed at any time when needed, but the information we give to relating companies is just general information, we'll never publish your identification.

**The Revision of the Privacy Policy**

The privacy policy of TestPassed improves continuously. With the expansion of our service area, we will update the privacy policy whenever there is something new. You can look over this notice at any time. Except for the large margin of revision in personal information, TestPassed won't inform the clients of the update. 

**Contact TestPassed**

If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices, please contact us: [**Contact now**](http://www.testpassed.com/contact.php)
